https://www.3dcs.com/dcs-privacy-policy

Understanding GD&T
What is GD&T?
Value of GD&T?
3DCS Features - Videos
What is Tolerance Analysis?
1D vs 2D vs 3D Tolerance Stacks
Understanding Worst Case
Statistical Process Control SPC
What is SPC?
QDM Analyst
QDM WEB (Site or Cloud)
System Deployments
Inspection Lab (BASIC)
Plant Level (SINGLE PLANT)
Enterprise Level (MULTI PLANT)
Contact
Contact DCS HQ (USA)
Understanding GD&T
What is GD&T?
Value of GD&T?
3DCS Features - Videos
What is Tolerance Analysis?
1D vs 2D vs 3D Tolerance Stacks
Understanding Worst Case
Statistical Process Control SPC
What is SPC?
QDM Analyst
QDM WEB (Site or Cloud)
System Deployments
Inspection Lab (BASIC)
Plant Level (SINGLE PLANT)
Enterprise Level (MULTI PLANT)
Contact
Contact DCS HQ (USA)
Understanding GD&T
What is GD&T?
Value of GD&T?
3DCS Features - Videos
What is Tolerance Analysis?
1D vs 2D vs 3D Tolerance Stacks
Understanding Worst Case
Statistical Process Control SPC
What is SPC?
QDM Analyst
QDM WEB (Site or Cloud)
System Deployments
Inspection Lab (BASIC)
Plant Level (SINGLE PLANT)
Enterprise Level (MULTI PLANT)
Contact
Contact DCS HQ (USA)
DCS Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy is meant to help you understand what data we collect, why we collect it, and what we do with it.
Privacy Policy
Our website includes a large variety of information. We try to keep you up to date on the latest innovations and releases, as well as events and training classes.
As part of this process, we sometimes collect information from our web visitors to learn which information is most interesting, and what content to provide more of.
This privacy policy includes the following to help you understand how we are handling the information we collect:
What information DCS collects
Where we store the information we collect
What DCS does with the information
Information DCS Collects
DCS collects information to provide better services to all of our users. This includes information about your browser, your language, region and company.
We collect information in the following ways:
Information you give us. Most of the information DCS collects is from the information you provide. This is done through forms on the website to gain access to content. This information is tied to your machine during your visit and stored as a cookie.
Information we get from your use of our website. DCS also collects information based on the pages you visit and the content you see. This occurs through the use of tracking scripts in the page code.
The specific information DCS collects from the website includes:
Pages visited
Source IP address
The information DCS collects from your use of the website may be associated with the information you provide DCS.
How We Use the Information We Collect
DCS uses the information that it collects to provide new and better content. DCS also uses this information to connect with visitors who have shown interest in DCS products and services.
DCS uses the information you provide to fill out additional forms while on the website. This makes it easier to access additional content without having to continually input personal information.
At all times, DCS wishes to respect your privacy. If you have any questions or concerns, please contact DCS at sales@3dcs.com.
Information we share
DCS does not share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of DCS with the following exceptions:
With your express consent
DCS will request the consent of individuals to share their information with third parties for use as a referral for services.
With DCS resellers (partners)
DCS shares information gathered from the website, such as a form from the Contact Us page, with its resellers. This information is provided to specific partners who may be in your region to provide better local support.
How Long Does DCS Retain Information
DCS holds records of visitors indefinitely within a secure database in Hubspot, a marketing platform. This information is limited:
1. Name
2. Email
3. Company
4. Country
Additional information may be collected via forms and will be retained as needed unless requested by the client. This information may be input into Salesforce and held there as a record of contact.
At any time, a client may contact DCS to:
1. Unsubscribe from specific or all communications
2. Have all their information removed from DCS Databases
CAN-SPAM Adherence
DCS respects the privacy of its customers and clients and adheres strictly to the CAN-SPAM laws established in 2003. This means that DCS will not add your name or email to mailing lists, nor provide it to a third party, without your permission.
General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Compliant
A processor of personal data must clearly disclose any data collection, declare the lawful basis and purpose for data processing, how long data is being retained, and if it is being shared with any third-parties or outside of the EU. Users have the right to request a portable copy of the data collected by a processor in a common format, and the right to have their data erased under certain circumstances.
As a result of these updates, DCS has taken the following actions:
1. Opt-in pop-up for accepting or declining cookies
2. Declared herein the use and purpose of data.
3. At any time have their information removed from DCS databases
4. Remove their email from any or all email services
In order to better serve you and improve the user experience, we are analyzing the audience of our site with Web Analytics solution: AFS Analytics. This service, which complies with the general data protection regulations, may save personal data (as defined by the GDPR) as a subcontractor, including a unique number consisting of alphanumeric characters identifying you.
This encrypted data is saved on secure servers located in France or in Canada. Canada guarantees data protection under Articles 44 and 46 of the GDPR. No banking information is transmitted to AFS Analytics.
We are the sole owner of the personally identifiable or not information data collected on our website. AFS Analytics does not share, sell, or claim any rights to this data. The storage duration is limited to 365 days by default.
You may request the deletion or modification of this data by contacting our Data Manager or DataSense, the company responsible for data for AFS Analytics.
For collecting data, we are using analytics.js, a library developed by AFS Analytics. This library uses cookie technology. The cookies are exclusively attached to our domain name, first-party Cookies and are not shared.
The data collected makes it possible to provide statistical traffic data. We are the sole owner of these cookies, and you can oppose their registration: Click here to opt out of AFS Analytics cookies
For any questions, or to have your information removed, please contact DCS at sales@3dcs.com with GDPR in the subject in the line.
Dimensional Control Systems, Inc
5750 New King Dr Ste 330Troy, Michigan, USA 48098Call us: +1-248-269-9777
FileShare (Downloads)
From Our Blog
Reach out to us
Copyright © 2020 Company, Inc. All Rights Reserved.
